Guide to the Theodore W. "Ted" Minah Records and Papers,1941-1975 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
Theodore W. Ted Minah records and papers 1941-1975 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
Minah, Theodore W., 1909-1991
41.4 linear feet Extent: 26,600 Items
Theodore W. Ted Minah, was the Director of Duke University Dining Halls from 1946-1974. Over his 28 years at Duke, Minah worked hard to serve the best quality food at as low a price as possible without incurring deficit to the University. By his retirement in 1974, Minah had transformed the dining halls at Duke University from a small operation to an operation of 12 dining halls serving approximately 15,000 meals per day. Materials in the collection include administrative records, work and purchase orders, food pricing, menus, financial and statistical reports, job descriptions, survey results, banquet logs, blueprints, union handbooks, black and white and color photographs, and other materials documenting the activities of the Duke University Dining Halls and the Director of Dining Halls.
UA.29.02.0007
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Provenance
The Theodore W. Ted Minah Records and Papers were received by the University Archives as a transfer in 1976 and 1981.
Biographical and Historical Note
Theodore W. Ted Minah, was the Director of Duke University Dining Halls from 1946-1974. Minah came to Duke at a time when it was necessary to convert the feeding operations from a war-time basis to that of feeding 5,000 students, and at a time where the situation of the dining halls was less than appealing. Over the next 28 years, Minah worked hard to serve the best quality food at as low a price as possible without incurring deficit to the University. During his tenure, he was responsible for many innovations to university dining services including establishing a food credit system, developing a program for student employees - where they recruited, trained and gave students opportunities to become head waiters and waitresses, and creating free-flow service counters which eliminated waiting lines in the cafeterias. Minah was also increased the capacity of dining halls to accommodate the growing number of students, including remodeling existing cafeterias into the University Room, Blue & White Room, and Cambridge Inn, and overseeing the construction of the award winning Gilbert-Addoms and Graduate Center dining halls.
Minah's career weathered the 1968 dining hall strike for "decent living wages" and several student food boycotts, including grapes (1969), lettuce (1972), and meat (1973). Despite these boycotts, Minah worked tirelessly to support and meet the needs of the students on both East and West campuses. In addition to his relationships with students, Minah also strongly supported his employees (a larger percentage of the employees were African American) by providing on-the-job training, finding summer jobs in North Carolina and out-of-state resorts, enabling them to combine vacation with extra income, and by providing the avenues for promotion into supervisory and cashier positions.
By his retirement in 1974, Minah had transformed the dining halls at Duke University from a small operation to an operation of 12 dining halls serving approximately 15,000 meals per day. Ted Minah died in 1991 at the age of 82.
Collection Overview
The Theodore W. "Ted" Minah records and papers span the years 1941-1975, with the bulk of the materials ranging from 1946-1974. The collection is arranged into three series: Administrative Records, 1945-1975, Articles and Speeches, 1941-1975 and Correspondence, 1945-1974. Administrative Records are further arranged into three subseries: Blueprints, Daily Banquet Logs, and General Administrative Records.
Materials in the collection include administrative records, correspondence, work and purchase orders, food pricing, menus, financial and statistical reports, job descriptions, survey results, banquet logs, blueprints, union handbooks, black and white and color photographs, and other materials documenting the activities of both the Duke University Dining Halls and the Director of Dining Halls, as well as well as Ted Minah's affiliations with professional associations.
Subject Headings
Cafeterias -- United States -- Employees; Duke University; Duke University. Dining Services; Duke University. Dining Halls; Duke University -- Students -- Political activity; Durham (N.C.) -- Race relations; Minah, Theodore W., 1909-1991; Photographs; Student housing -- North Carolina -- Durham; Universities and colleges -- Food service
Related Material
Inventory of the Dining Services Reference Collection, 1945-2001
University Archives, Duke University.
Inventory of the Duke Vigil Collection, 1968-1988
University Archives, Duke University.
Inventory of the Office of the University Treasurer records, 1893-1982
University Archives, Duke University.
Inventory of the Radio TV Service Records, circa 1937-1988
University Archives, Duke University.
Inventory of the University Archives Photograph Collection, 1861-ongoing
University Archives, Duke University.
Inventory of the WDBS Collection, 1949-1983
University Archives, Duke University.
Contents of Collection
- Administrative Records,1945-1975 and undated
  - Blueprints,1947-1971 and undated, About 50 items
    Includes oversized blueprints of detailed renovations, alterations, installations, and floor plans of primarily Duke campus dining halls (East and West), kitchens, buildings, and equipment systems. The blueprints are located drawers 31/32 in the map cabinets.
    - Union Building – Women’s College Floor Plan, undated (Horace Trumbauer, Architect) (Folder 1)
    - Union Building – West Campus, 1962
    - Union Building – West Campus, 1962
    - Proposed Dish Room Plan – Union Building – West Campus, 1962
    - Equipment Details – Union Building – West Campus, 1962
    - Union Building Renovation – Floor Plan, 1971 (Folder 2)
    - Duke West – First Floor, 1962
    - Equipment – Union – West Campus, 1962
    - Gilbert-Addoms Floor Plan, 1955
    - Union Building – West Campus – Subveyor System “B”, 1962
    - Union Building – West Campus – Dish Table Assembly, 1962
    - Duke University Chemistry Building Floor Plans, undated
    - S.S. Shelving for Kitchen – Men’s Union, 1955 (Folder 3)
    - Alterations to Union Building – West Campus, 1962
    - Dishwasher Installation, 1962
    - Union Building Floor Plan, 1962
    - Student Activities Building, undated
    - Union Building – West Campus, 1962 (Floor Plans/Equipment)
    - Alterations to Union Building, 1962
    - Union – West Campus – Floor Plan, 1954 (Folder 4)
    - Cambridge Inn, 1967
    - Equipment – The Woman’s College, 1957
    - Equipment – Men’s Dormitory – West Campus, 1950
    - Proposed Subveyors – Union Building, 1968 (Folder 5)
    - Union Building – West Campus – Light Panel, 1962
    - Proposed Alterations – Dining Halls, Duke Marine Laboratory, Beaufort, NC, 1957
    - Dishwashing Counter – Dining Hall, Beaufort, NC, 1960
    - Highland Hospital, Asheville, NC, 1957
    - Highland Hospital, Asheville, NC, 1957
    - Highland Hospital, Asheville, NC, 1957
    - Union Building – West Campus Floor Plan, 1954 (Folder 6)
    - Union Building – West Campus Basement Floor Plan, 1954
    - Conveyor System – Women’s Union Building, 1951
    - Air Conditioning – Great Hall and Gothic Hall – Union Building, 1970 (Folder 7)
    - Men’s Union, undated
    - Union Building, 1968
    - West Campus Union – Basement Renovation, 1965
    - Renovation of Walk-In Refrigerator (Section A, B, C, D & E), 1964
    - Cash Register Table – Blue & White Room, 1962
    - Basement Floor Plan – Men’s Union Building, undated
    - Dining Halls, Men’s Union, 1947
    - Arrangement of Dishwashing Pantry – Men’s Graduate Center, 1950
    - Cafeteria Counters – Women’s Union Building, 1952
    - Subbasement Floor Plan – Graduate Men’s Dormitory, 1950
    - Basement Floor Plan – Graduate Men’s Dormitory, 1950
    - Basement Floor Plan – Graduate Men’s Dormitory, 1950
    - Proposed Arrangement for New Location of Subveyor #1, 1971
    - Part Plan – Basement, undated
    - Part Plan – 2nd Floor, undated
    - Model 85PT Dishwasher with Prewash from Water Main, 1952
    - Oak Room – Service Kitchen, undated (Folder 8)
    - Hot Food Table for Oak Room Service Kitchen, 1957
    - Proposed Alterations – Oak Room Kitchen, 1957
    - Rearrangement of Oak Room Serving Kitchen, 1957
    - Revised Drawing of Subveyor Unit – Oak Room, 1957
    - Student Union Building, University of Kentucky, 1966
    - Duke University, 1967
    - Proposed Office Layout for Duke Endowment Fund, 1961
    - Ground Floor – Gilbert-Addoms, undated
    - Indoor Stadium (copy), 1939
    - Floor Plan – Rooms 109, 109D, 112B – Union Building, 1966 (Folder 9)
    - Conveyor System – Women’s Union Building, 1951
    - Second Floor Plan – Building, University of New Hampshire, undated
    - Second Floor Plan – Building, University of New Hampshire, undated
    - Proposed Alterations to Entrance to Oak Room, 1955
    - 1st and 2nd Floor Plan, undated
    - Model “F” Subveyor (Reversible), 1952
    - Subveyor System, 1950
  - Daily Banquet Logs,1948-1974
    6.0 ln. ft. (27 items)
    Arrangement: chronologically
    Each annual log contains details of daily dining hall events and banquets, handwritten menus, receipts, brochures, and banquet requests/cancellation letters.
    - Daily Banquet Logs, 1948-1955 (Box 1)
    - Daily Banquet Logs, 1956-1961 (Box 2)
    - Daily Banquet Logs, 1962-1968 (Box 3)
    - Daily Banquet Logs, 1969-1974 (Box 4)
  - General Administrative Records,1945-1975 and undated
    23.3 ln. ft. (about 17,500 items)
    Arrangement: Alphabetically
    Materials in this subseries include administrative records, work and purchase orders, food pricing, menus, financial and statistical reports, job descriptions, survey results, union handbooks, black and white and color photographs, and other materials documenting the activities of the Duke University Dining Halls and the Director of Dining Halls.
    - Administrative Aid Book (Box 5)
    - Air Conditioning – Great Hall and Gothic Dining Hall, 1970 (Box 5)
    - Auditorium, 1958 (Box 5)
    - Average Checks, 1946 (Box 5)
    - Average Check Report, 1957 Jan (Box 5)
    - Ballroom, 1952 (Box 5)
    - Ballroom – Cost of New Floor, 1964, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Banquet Survey, 1952-1953 (Box 5)
    - Beer Sales on Campus, 1971 (Box 5)
    - Black and White Photos of Duke Dining Halls, 1946, 1950, 1964 and undated (Box 5)
    - Blueprint – Subveyor – Oak Room to Kitchen, 1957 (Box 5)
    - Blueprints – Blue and White Room, undated (Box 5)
    - Blueprints– Oak Room Service Kitchen, 1957 (Box 5)
    - Break Even Report, 1951 (Box 5)
    - Brewster Corp. – Display Panels (Box 5)
    - Board Contract, 1971-1972 (Box 5)
    - Board Contract – East Campus, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
    - Board Survey, 1973 Nov (Box 5)
    - Board Survey – East Campus, 1971 Nov (Box 5)
    - Budget Sheets – Originals, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
    - Buffet Meals – In Gothic Reading Room, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
    - Bulletin of Duke University (Box 5)
    - Cafeteria Prices, 1945 (Box 5)
    - Cafeteria Prices, 1951 (Box 6)
    - Cafeteria Prices, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Cafeteria Prices - West, 1966-1971 (Box 6)
    - Cambridge Inn, 1966-1971 (Box 6)
    - Cambridge Inn – Newspaper Clippings, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Cambridge Inn – Renovations, 1966-1967 (Box 6)
    - Campus Planning Studies, 1959-1968 (Box 6)
    - Cancer Research Dinner, 1975 Nov 20 (Box 6)
    - Capacities of Dining Rooms for Emergency Feeding, 1950 (Box 6)
    - Career Guidance (Box 6)
    - Carolina Times, 1967 Sept 16 (Box 6)
    - Carrier Ice Maker, undated (Box 6)
    - Cashiers – Job Analysis (Box 6)
    - Chesterfield Show, 1953 (Box 6)
    - Christmas Party – Employees, 1957, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Class 1971 – Sophomore Father’s Weekend, 1969 Apr (Box 6)
    - Cleland Celebration, 1974 (Box 6)
    - Color Photos of Duke Dining Halls, undated (Box 6)
    - Assorted Photographs from 1930s Productions (Box 6)
    - Columbia University 1199 Contract, 1969 (Box 7)
    - College Unions (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1947 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1948 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1950 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1952 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1953 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1954 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1955 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1956 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1957 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1958 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1959-1962 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1963 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1967 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1972-1973 (Box 7)
    - Cooperative Food Services Project – Durham City Schools (Box 7)
    - Correspondence – Kotschevar (Box 7)
    - Correspondence – School of Forestry (Box 7)
    - Correspondence – Woman’s College Dining Halls, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
    - Cost Percentages – Comparisons (Box 7)
    - Council on Leaders and Specialists (CLS) of the Experimental International Living (Box 7)
    - Daily Report, 1946 (Box 7)
    - Davison (W.C.) Dinner, 1961 (Folder 1) (Box 7)
    - Davison (W.C.) Dinner, 1961 (Folder 2) (Box 7)
    - Dean Herring’s Retirement, 1956 (Box 8)
    - Dean’s Meeting (Role at Dining Hall), 1965 (Box 8)
    - Dedication of Paul Gross Chemistry Building, 1969 (Box 8)
    - Deferred Revenue Board and Board Students-East Campus, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
    - Dietary Clinic – Graduate Center (Box 8)
    - Dining Hall – Catering and Banquet Prices, 1957 (Box 8)
    - Dining Hall Prices, 1973 (Box 8)
    - Dining Hall Prices, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Director of Dining Halls (Box 8)
    - Distributive Education (Box 8)
    - Dogs (Box 8)
    - Dormitories – Men’s Residence Halls, 1967 (Box 8)
    - Draft (Military) (Box 8)
    - D.U.D.H. Specials – Combinations Survey, 1965 (Box 8)
    - Duke and Duchess Magazine (Box 8)
    - Duke Dining Halls – Manpower Requirements and New Goals, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Duke Endowment, 1962 Dec 10 (Box 8)
    - Duke Endowment Office Layout (Box 8)
    - Duke Endowment Reception, 1962 May, 1965 (Box 8)
    - Duke Football Dinner, 1958 (Box 8)
    - Duke Forms & Charts (Box 8)
    - Duke Graduate Dormitory – Wright Co., 1950-1951 (Box 8)
    - Duke Handbooks (Employment/Union), 1965-1972 and undated (Box 8)
    - Duke Symposium, 1967 (Box 8)
    - Duke University Dining Halls Cost Report Forms (Box 8)
    - Duke University Hospital – Dietetics Department, 1959-1962 (Box 8)
    - Durham City Schools (Box 8)
    - East Campus – Residence Halls (Box 9)
    - East Campus – Summer, 1958 (Box 9)
    - East Campus Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
    - East Campus Dining Hall Remodeling, 1972 (Box 9)
    - East Campus Dining Halls, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
    - East Campus Dining Halls – Manning Tables (Box 9)
    - East Campus Dining Halls Budget Worksheets, 1972 (Box 9)
    - East Campus Faculty Dining Room - Draperies (Box 9)
    - East Campus Payroll, 1958-1959 (Box 9)
    - Employee – Wage Classification (Box 9)
    - Employee Comparison, 1962-1963 (Box 9)
    - Employee Criticism – Hattie Williams, 1966-1971 (Box 9)
    - Employee Meals (Policy Memo No. 4) (Box 9)
    - Employee Reviews and Referrals, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
    - Employees’ Christmas Party, 1955 (Box 9)
    - Employees’ Luncheon (20+ years), 1968 (Box 9)
    - Employees’ Luncheon (30+ years), 1968 (Box 9)
    - Employees – Hospitalization Insurance (Box 9)
    - Employees – Hourly (Box 9)
    - Employees – Human Relations and Communications Course (Box 9)
    - Employees – Luncheon for 10 Year and Older (Box 9)
    - Employees – Request for Use of Hospital Facilities (Sick Leave) (Box 9)
    - Employees - Seniority Policy (Box 9)
    - Examples of Union Contracts, Policies, Etc., 1968 (Box 9)
    - Faculty Christmas Dinner, 1962 Dec 15 (Box 10)
    - Faculty Christmas Party, 1965-1966 (Box 10)
    - Faculty Club, 1961-1964 (Box 10)
    - Faculty Club – Program, 1957-1958 (Box 10)
    - Faculty Club Christmas Party, 1952-1959 (Box 10)
    - Faculty Club Christmas Party, 1961-1964 (Box 10)
    - Faculty Club Reception for Dr. & Mrs. Knight, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Faculty Dining Facilities Committee, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Fast for Rebirth of Compassion, 1967 (Box 10)
    - Financial Reports of East Campus Dining Halls, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
    - Flow Charts, 1948-1950 (Box 10)
    - Flow Charts – Customer Counts (Box 10)
    - Food Control Yields & Portions (Box 10)
    - Food Cost Control System, 1947 (Box 10)
    - Food Handler’s School, 1962 Oct (Box 10)
    - Food Management Magazine (Box 10)
    - Food Price Study and Recommendation (Duke and Neighboring Institutions) (Box 10)
    - Food Prices, 1965-1967 (Box 10)
    - Food Service Information, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
    - Food Service School, 1968 Oct 16-18 (Box 10)
    - Food Services Brochure, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Football – Official 1967 Program with DUDH Ad (Box 10)
    - Foreign Students (Box 10)
    - Forms Used on East Campus (Box 11)
    - Founders Day – 100th Anniversary, 1956 (Box 11)
    - Fraternities – Letter to President on East Dining Halls, 1967 Mar (Box 11)
    - Freshman Week History (Box 11)
    - Fruit & Vegetables, 1964-1965 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center, 1950-1952 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Background Music (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Coffee Lounge Late Business, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Feeding Nurses (Box 11)
    - [Men’s] Graduate Center – Job Analysis, 1955 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Job Descriptions (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Original Orders for Supplies, 1951 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Payroll, 1955-1956 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Personnel (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Report on Use, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Spring Holidays, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Spring Recess Closing, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Summer, 1953, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Supplies Inventories, 1952-1953 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center – Wallpaper Description, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center Banquet Use, 1952-1953 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center Cost Summaries, 1953-1973 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center Dining Hall Operating Statements, 1952-1953 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center Dining Hall Operating Statements, 1953-1954 (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center Floor Plans (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center Letters (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center Opening – Invitation and Letters (Box 11)
    - Graduate Center Regulations – Dean Herring, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Gilbert-Addoms, 1956-1960 (Box 11)
    - Gilbert-Addoms - Correspondence (Box 11)
    - Gilbert-Addoms Class Dinners (Box 12)
    - Grapes Boycott, 1969 (Box 12)
    - Great Hall Layout, 1963 (Box 12)
    - Guides, undated (Box 12)
    - Guidelines – Union Election, 1967-1972 (Box 12)
    - Health Department – Food Service School (Box 12)
    - Health Dept. Ratings, 1945-1959 (Box 12)
    - Highland Hospital, 1967-1970 (Box 12)
    - Hillside High – Distributive Education, 1962-1964 (Box 12)
    - Hillside High School, 1968 (Box 12)
    - Homecoming, 1947-1950 (Box 12)
    - Homecoming, 1951 (Box 12)
    - Homecoming, 1952 (Box 12)
    - Homecoming Barbecue, 1953 (Box 12)
    - Homecoming Barbecue, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Homecoming Barbecue, 1955-1959 (Box 12)
    - Homecoming Barbecue, 1959-1971 (Box 12)
    - Hospital Auxiliary Dinner, 1975 Nov 20 (Box 12)
    - Hotel Thesis (PhD) – Doris Elizabeth King (Box 12)
    - Housing Report (Parker) (Box 12)
    - [Mr. Hamilton] Hoyler – Central Warehouse, 1963-1964 (Box 12)
    - Inauguration – Dr. Edens, 1949 (Box 12)
    - Inauguration – Dr. Knight, 1963 (Box 13)
    - Inauguration – President Terry Sanford, 1970 (Box 13)
    - Inauguration Messages, 1949 (Box 13)
    - Incidents (Box 13)
    - Indoor Stadium (copy), 1939 (Box 13)
    - Industrial Education Center – Mr. Simpson (Box 13)
    - Insignia (Duke) (Box 13)
    - Institutional Self-Study in the Area of Student Affairs (Box 13)
    - Institutions Award Photo, undated (Box 13)
    - Institutions Contest, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Institutions Contest Entry, 1952-1953 (Box 13)
    - Institutions Magazine, 1961-1967 (Box 13)
    - Institutions Magazine Contest – Gilbert-Addoms, 1959 (Box 13)
    - International Student Orientation, 1964 (Box 13)
    - Job Description – Gilbert-Addoms, 1962 (Box 13)
    - Labor Relations, Unions, Labor Laws, etc., 1967-1968 and undated (Box 14)
    - Law School – Serving Areas for Seminars, 1964-1975 (Box 14)
    - Layout West Campus Union, 1973 (Box 14)
    - Lettuce Boycott, 1972-1973 (Box 14)
    - Local 77 AFSCME Contract, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Long Range Plan (Box 14)
    - Long Range Plan – Dining Halls, 1966 (Box 14)
    - Long Range Planning Studies, 1950-1960 (Box 14)
    - Long Range Planning Studies, 1961-1964 (Box 14)
    - Margaret Hart Wedding, 1961 Jun 8 (Box 15)
    - Meal Census – Woman’s College (Box 15)
    - Meal Hours – West Campus, 1968-1970 (Box 15)
    - Meals Served – Summer School, 1965-1966 (Box 15)
    - Meat Boycott, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Medical Self Help Training Course (Box 15)
    - Memos – Dining Hall Employees, 1968-1969 (Box 15)
    - Men’s Campus Renovation, 1956-1957 (Box 15)
    - Men’s Dining Hall Operating Statements, 1951-1952 (Box 15)
    - Men’s Dining Hall Operating Statements, 1952-1953 (Box 15)
    - Men’s Dining Hall Operating Statements, 1953-1954 (Box 15)
    - Men’s Graduate Center – Sunday Opening, 1967 Feb (Box 15)
    - Menu Selections – East Campus Dining Halls (Box 15)
    - Menus – East Campus, 1974 (Box 15)
    - Menus – West Campus Cafeteria, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Menus & Prices – Duke and UNC, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Methodist Youth Fellowship, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Middle East Forum, 1968 Mar (Box 15)
    - Milk Contract, 1953 (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1951 and undated (Box 15)
    - M.I.T. Report on Student Staff (Box 15)
    - Monthly Ration Report, 1954 (Box 15)
    - Moratorium, 1969 Oct 15 (Box 15)
    - Move to Men’s Graduate Center, 1960 (Box 15)
    - M.S.G.A. (Men’s Student Government Association) (Box 15)
    - M.S.G.A. – Dining Room Hours, 1955 (Box 15)
    - M.S.G.A. – University Store Comm. (Box 15)
    - M.S.G.A. (Men’s Student Government Association) Catering Service Photos, 1951 (Box 15)
    - Naval ROTC Seminar, 1970 (Box 16)
    - New Payroll – I.B.M., 1954 (Box 16)
    - New Residential Hall (Gilbert-Addoms), 1955-1957 (Box 16)
    - North Carolina Academy – Dinner, 1967 May 12 (Box 16)
    - North Carolina College (Box 16)
    - North Carolina Press Association Dinner, 1947-1963 (Box 16)
    - North Carolina Press Association Dinner, 1967-1971 (Box 16)
    - North Carolina State Board of Health – Inspection Forms (Box 16)
    - Nursing Students – Food Service Information, 1965-1966 (Box 16)
    - Nursing Students Summer Board, 1962 (Box 16)
    - Oak Room, 1958-1959 (Box 16)
    - Oak Room – Customer Count, 1965 Jan-Mar (Box 16)
    - Oak Room – General Correspondence (Box 16)
    - Oak Room – Labor Cost Survey, 1960-1961 (Box 16)
    - Oak Room – Renovation (Ron O’Kelley Report), 1966 (Box 16)
    - Oak Room – Specials (Box 16)
    - Oak Room Analysis (Box 16)
    - Oak Room and Cafeteria Price Information, 1972 (Box 16)
    - Oak Room Decorations (Box 16)
    - Oak Room Drapes 1972 (Box 16)
    - Oak Room Incidents (Box 16)